

CONTACT ME AT

- Prk. Rizal 1-B, Canocotan
 Tagum City, Davao Del Norte
 Philippines
- emmanagan092495@gmail.com

SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• Web Development
- ●●●● Mobile Development (Android/IOS)
- •••• Game Development
- ••• IOT Development

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY, NODE, PHP, WORDPRESS, DRUPAL, SASS, REACT, REACT NATIVE, PHASER, FIREBASE

EMMANUEL AGAN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I want to succeed in a stimulating and challenging environment, building the success of the company or individual, while I experience advanced opportunities where I can apply my skills and knowledge, to design and implement innovative and efficient technical projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Milbank Motel | 2020

- Determining operational practicality
- Identifying areas for modification in existing programs and subsequently developing these modifications

Software Developer

Swapee | 2020

- Developing application programming interfaces (APIs) to support mobile functionality
- Using and adapting existing web applications for apps

Software Developer

Burn Media Group | 2019

- Conduct day-to-day project coordination, planning, and implementation across multiple teams
- Create functional and technical application documents

Software Developer

Texperts | 2019

- Managed complex projects from start to finish
- Deploying software tools, processes and metrics
- Translated requirements into polished, high-level designs

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Simple Nursing | 2018 - 2019

- Plan and implement new designs
- Optimize existing user interface designs
- Test for intuitivity and experience

Junior Web Developer

FSTech | 2017 - 2018

- Researching, designing, implementing and managing software programs
- Developing quality assurance procedures

EDUCATION

Elementary School

Don Ricardo Briz Elementary School | S.Y 2001-2006

Secondary School

Tagum City National High School | S.Y 2006-2010

College School

STI Tagum City(BSIT) | S.Y 2010-2014